let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "All of the gases on the planet make up the earth's…",
        answer: "b. Atmosphere",
        options: [
            "a. Biosphere",
            "b. Atmosphere",
            "c. Barometer",
            "d. Climate"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "The pattern of weather conditions over many years is called…",
        answer: "b. Climate",
        options: [
            "a. Forecast",
            "b. Climate",
            "c. Temperature",
            "d. Atlas"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "The increase in the average temperature of the earth's atmosphere is referred to by scientists as…",
        answer: "a. Global heating",
        options:[
            "a. Global heating",
            "b. Thermo-climate",
            "c. Earth charge",
            "d. Core temperature change"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "What is the name of gas released into the atmosphere when we burn fossil fuel for energy like coal, oil and natural gas?",
        answer: "c. Carbon dioxide (CO2)",
        options: [
            "a. Plutonium",
            "b. Oxygen",
            "c. Carbon dioxide (CO2)",
            "d. Hydrogen"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "Which of the following sectors does not contribute to greenhouse gas emissions?",
        answer: "d. They all do",
        options: [
            "a. Transportation",
            "b. Deforestation",
            "c. Agriculture",
            "d. They all do"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "Which could be a direct/indirect impact of climate change on children's health?",
        answer: "d. All of the above",
        options: [
            "a. Lack of access to healthcare due to migration",
            "b. Shortened food supply and poor nutrition",
            "c. Limited access to clean water and increased water borne illness",
            "d. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "What are the gases called that become trapped in the earth's atmosphere and are heating the planet?",
        answer: "c. Greenhouse gases",
        options: [
            "a. Humidity",
            "b. Precipitation",
            "c. Greenhouse gases",
            "d. Nitrates"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "What did countries agree to in the famous “Paris Agreement” in 2015?",
        answer: "a. To keep global temperature rise below 2°C and pursue a path to limit warming to 1.5°C",
        options: [
            "a. To keep global temperature rise below 2°C and pursue a path to limit warming to 1.5°C",
            "b. To stop countries from dumping rubbish in the ocean",
            "c. To transition to all electric cars by 2050",
            "d. To plant 1 million trees in deforested areas"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "Which one of the activities below is an action you can take to reduce your carbon footprint?",
        answer: "d. All of the above",
        options: [
            "a. Eat less meat",
            "b. Plant a tree",
            "c. Wear second-hand fashion",
            "d. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "Which is the most important day young people can take action on climate change?",
        answer: "c. Every day",
        options: [
            "a. Earth Day",
            "b. World Environment Day",
            "c. Every day",
            "d. World Cleanup Day"
        ]
    },
];